Okay, for those who need some more additional handholding,
this is how you'll actually update the
curated two aggregated jobs.
You already have it here, right?
The script one, the curated aggregated script.
Click on this and uh, get the code from, uh, the video below
or the previous video and, uh, open it in your VS code.
Copy the whole code, go back and paste it,
and then finally save it.
And let's go to job details
and make sure you do enable the job bookmark.
Then save it. And then
before you run, just take a look at the script.
The script has all the checks
for making sure the bookmark runs fine.
So we have job in it here
and we have all the code under that
and between essentially job dot commit as well.
Okay, before that as well, in fact.
And then we are creating the dynamic frame from the catalog.
And this time the table name is curated H-V-F-H-V.
Remember, we got this created
for the data analyst to look at.
And of course we also have the transformation.
This is required for the job book part to work fine.
And then finally, you simply just run the job.
That's pretty much it. And, um, this will run fine
and it'll load the data to aggregate layer
and then give a try by running yourself again.
That part I will not show.
So let this run once and go to your S3 bucket.
And you should see an aggregate folder here when,
when it's all done, and this would've already succeeded.
Run it again and look at the CloudWatch
log by clicking on this.
And you should see that there was no new data to load.
Okay, get that done. Talk to you soon.